here are the stories were covering this
これは物語がこれをカバーしていた
week in the category 5 TV newsroom an
カテゴリー5のテレビニュースルームでの週
Airbus a350 software bug forces the
エアバスa350ソフトウェアのバグにより、
airlines to turn planes off and on again
航空会社が飛行機の電源を入れ直します
every 4 149 hours virgins Hyperloop one
4 149時間ごとに処女Hyperloop 1
company has signed a deal with the
会社はとの取り引きに署名しました
government of Saudi Arabia to build a
サウジアラビア政府が建設する
test track for its futuristic transport
その未来の輸送のためのテストトラック
concept yet another crowdfunded game has
コンセプト別のクラウドファンディングゲームが持っています
become an exclusive to the epic game
壮大なゲームの独占になる
store MechWarrior 5 mercenaries release
ストアMechWarrior 5 en兵リリース
has been delayed to December and won't
12月に遅れており、
be on Steam as its backers expected and
支援者が期待するとおりにSteamに参加し、
you can run Android on Nintendo switch
ニンテンドースイッチでAndroidを実行できます
and it runs entirely from your SD card
それは完全にあなたのSDカードから実行されます
that's right the built-in OS remains
そうです、組み込みOSはそのままです
intact and you can jump back and forth
無傷で前後にジャンプできます
between os's by simply rebooting these
これらのOSを再起動するだけで
stories are coming right up
物語はすぐに来ています
don't go anywhere this is the category 5
これはカテゴリー5ですどこにも行かないでください
dot TV newsroom covering the week's top
今週のトップをカバーするドットテレビニュースルーム
tech stories with a slight linux bias
わずかなLinuxバイアスのあるテクノロジーストーリー
i'm sasha Rickman and here the top
私はサーシャ・リックマンです
stories for following this week an
今週をフォローするための物語
airbus a350 software bug forces the
エアバスa350ソフトウェアのバグにより、
airlines to turn planes off and on again
航空会社が飛行機の電源を入れ直します
every 149 hours some models of the
149時間ごとに
airliners still need to be hard rebooted
旅客機はまだハードリブートする必要があります
after exactly 149 hours despite warnings
警告にもかかわらず正確に149時間後
from the EU Aviation Safety Agency or
EU Aviation Safety Agencyまたは
ESA first issued two years ago in a
ESAは2年前に最初に発行されました
mandatory air were the air worthiness
必須の空気は空気の価値でした
directive reissued just over a week ago
指令は1週間以上前に再発行されました
eásá urged operators to turn their a350s
eásáは、オペレーターにA350を有効にするよう促しました
off and on again to prevent quote
オフとオンを繰り返して引用を防止します
partial or total loss of some avionics
一部のアビオニクスの部分的または全体的な損失
systems or functions and both the
システムまたは機能と両方
revised directive effective from July 26
7月26日から施行される改訂指令
exempts only those new a3 59:40 ones
これらの新しいa3 59:40のみを除外します
which have been had which had been
持っていた持っていた
modified had modified software preloaded
変更されたソフトウェアはプリロードされていました
on the production line for all other
他のすべての生産ラインで
a350 not 9:40 once operators still need
オペレーターがまだ必要な9:40ではなくa350
to completely power the airliner down
旅客機を完全にパワーダウンするために
before it reaches 149 hours of
149時間に達する前に
continuous power on time concerning Lee
リーに関する継続的なパワーオン時間
the original directive was brought in
元の指令が持ち込まれた
brought about in 2017 by quote
2017年に引用によってもたらされた
in-service event where a loss of
稼働中のイベント
communication occurred between some
いくつかの間で通信が発生しました
avionics systems and avionics and
アビオニクスシステムとアビオニクス
networks and quote the impact of the
ネットワークとの影響を引用
failures arranged from redundancy loss
冗長性損失から整理された障害
to quote complete loss on a specific
特定の完全な損失を引用する
function hosted on common remotes data
共通のリモートデータでホストされる機能
concentrator and core processing
コンセントレーターとコア処理
input/output modules and quote in lay
入力/出力モジュールとレイアウトの引用
terms this means at that prior to 2017
これは2017年以前のことを意味する用語
at least some a350s flying passengers
少なくとも一部のa350の乗客
were suffering unexplained failures of
原因不明の失敗に苦しんでいた
potentially flight critical digital
フライトクリティカルな可能性のあるデジタル
systems it is common for airliners to be
旅客機にとって一般的なシステム
left powered on while parked at airport
空港に駐車中に電源を入れたままにする
gates so maintainer x' can carry out
メンテナーx 'が実行できるゲート
routine system checks between flights
フライト間の定期的なシステムチェック
especially if the aircraft is plugged
特に航空機が詰まっている場合
into ground power the remedy for the
地上電力への救済策
a350 941 problem is straightforward
a350 941の問題は簡単です
install airbus software updates for a
エアバスソフトウェアアップデートのインストール
permanent cure or switch the aeroplane
恒久的な治療または飛行機の切り替え
off and on again affected airlines are
オフとオンに再び影響を受ける航空会社は
Air France
エアフランス
American Airlines Delta Air Lines and
アメリカン航空のデルタ航空と
Lufthansa as well as air chat air China
ルフトハンザおよびエアチャットエアチャイナ
and Taiwan's China Airlines hmm hmm Wow
そして台湾のチャイナエアラインズうーんうーんうわー
so they don't actually say what the
彼らは実際に何を言っていない
critical failures may be wait Henry what
重大な失敗は、ヘンリーが何を待つかです
kind of failures could you have that
一種の失敗
would lead to Boeing's not alone anymore
ボーイングはもう一人ではありません
I'm just kidding no um no it's if it was
冗談じゃないよ
more critical there would be more
もっと重大な
Porsche about it like we saw with the
私たちが見たようなポルシェ
737 max yeah be like the toilet doesn't
737 maxそうそうトイレはそうではない
flush or something yeah no problem yeah
フラッシュまたは何かええ問題ないええ
again it's when you're talking about
再びそれはあなたが話しているときです
that kind of stuff I'm guessing that
そういうものだと思う
it's pulley non-critical systems so like
それは滑車の非重要なシステムです
if it's just like because there are
あるからといって
things days your digital nowadays yeah
昨今のデジタル時代
right especially with Airbus planes
特にエアバス機で
because Airbus believes the philosophy
エアバスは哲学を信じているため
of the plane knows how to fly well as
飛行機のようにうまく飛ぶ方法を知っています
Boeing thinks that the pilot knows how
ボーイングはパイロットがその方法を知っていると考えています
to fly so in a Boeing plane you can
ボーイング機で飛ぶには
normally stall the plane as a pilot but
通常、パイロットとして飛行機を失速させますが、
an Airbus plan you can't because it's
エアバスプランは
all electronic right like they entrust
彼らが委託するようなすべての電子的権利
the plane war so to hear that they have
彼らが持っていることを聞くために飛行機戦争
like such a technical issue on an Airbus
エアバスのような技術的な問題のような
plane is kind of concerning right
飛行機は一種の権利です
because it's just it
それだけだから
more electronically controlled than a
より電子的に制御される
standard moon plane right but again
標準の月面
everything's fly-by-wire nowadays
今日のすべてはフライバイワイヤです
everything's electronically controlled
すべてが電子的に制御されている
so hopefully it's nothing too critical
うまくいけば、それはあまりにも重要ではない
yeah like controls or anything but well
ええ、コントロールなどが好きです
the the other question is how easy is it
もう一つの質問はそれがどれほど簡単かです
to turn a plane off and on like is it
飛行機の電源を入れたり切ったりするのは
something you could conceivably just do
おそらくあなたができること
preemptively before any flight yeah it's
フライトの前に先制的にはい
it's not hard to do but as we saw with
難しいことではありませんが、私たちが見たように
today's earlier story it does take time
今日の以前の話には時間がかかります
for instruments to know where they are
楽器がどこにあるかを知るために
you have to put in your like exact
あなたのような正確に置く必要があります
coordinates again you have to do all
もう一度調整する必要があります
that stuff so in an industry where time
時間のかかる業界では
is money yeah it adds time right so why
お金ですよね。時間を追加するので、なぜ
not just you keep certain systems on if
特定のシステムをオンにしておくだけでなく
it's a quick turnaround then go hmm but
それは速いターンアラウンドであり、その後うーん行きますが、
yeah so don't be silly update your
ええ、あなたを愚かに更新しないでください
planes
飛行機
yeah because I'm thinking like you're
ええ、私はあなたのように考えているからです
you're talking delayed flights exactly
あなたは正確に遅延便を話している
you're sitting on a tarmac having to
あなたはしなければならないターマックに座っています
reboot the computer and go through all
コンピューターを再起動し、すべてを実行します
the pre-flight checks and everything
プリフライトチェックとすべて
else right but there are times when the
それ以外の場合は正しいが、
plate plane doesn't like seem to be
プレート面が好きではないようです
doing anything now I know that it is but
今何でもしているが、
it doesn't seem to be like when it's
それがそうであるときのようではないようです
getting the ice through the winter it's
冬の間に氷を得る
sitting on the tarmac and it's just
駐機場に座って、それだけです
being sprayed could you then power it
スプレーされたら、電源を入れることができますか
off and power back on and that man I
オフにして電源を入れ直します
don't know like this the systems that
このようなシステムを知らない
they're talking about sounds like their
彼らは彼らのような音について話している
flight critical systems so going on my
フライトクリティカルなシステム
point from before again like the CEO
CEOのように再び前からポイントする
like the gyros and stuff at each gate
各ゲートのジャイロやスタッフのように
they have the assign like geo exact
彼らは正確な地理のような割り当てを持っています
coordinate so like your inertial units
慣性ユニットのように調整します
can't turn those off because then you'd
それらをオフにすることはできません
have to go back and like read it and put
戻って読むのが好き
the numbers so like if you're in like an
あなたがいるような場合のように数字
iced in airport where you're like
あなたが好きな空港でアイス
sitting down there for like two or three
そこに2〜3回座って
hours they wouldn't be able to turn it
彼らはそれを変えることができないだろう時間
off right so that's that's time on the
オフになっているので、それは時間です
hour
時
now Henry I've only ever flown a drone
今ヘンリー私は今までドローンを飛ばしたことがない
how do they take an Airbus and flip it
彼らはどのようにエアバスを取り、それを反転しますか
over
以上
and turn oh I guess just update like the
そして、ああ、私はちょうどのように更新すると思います
software just update your software yeah
ソフトウェアはソフトウェアを更新するだけです
is there any cost like do they like it
彼らはそれを好きですかのようなコストはありますか
stop them from updating the sideways
彼らが横向きに更新するのを止める
point it's almost like updating your
それはあなたの更新のようなものです
iPad or like they running Windows
iPadまたはWindowsを実行しているユーザー
the main issue is that in aviation
主な問題は、航空
everything's so scrutinized right Celaya
すべてが非常に精査された右セラヤ
in the for example they have to be
例えば、彼らは
improved in the FAA in the states like
のような州のFAAで改善
every single update right so um and
ひとつひとつの更新が正しいように
Europe's really hard about that as well
ヨーロッパもそれについて本当に難しい
as same here in Canada like they have to
カナダでも同じように
prove each and every update by the
すべての更新を証明する
government whoever starting the
政府の誰でも
authority right so I did notice that
権限があります
Canadian Airlines words on the list of
のリストにあるカナダ航空の言葉
the affected Airlines does that mean we
影響を受ける航空会社はそれを意味します
just don't have these planes yeah we
これらの飛行機を持っていません
just don't have those models oh right so
ちょうどそれらのモデルを持っていません
like um yeah for example WestJet only
ええええ、たとえばウェストジェットのみ
has smaller planes right so yeah yeah
小さい飛行機があります
we're we're safe guys I just wondered
私たちは無事だと思った
maybe we weren't affected because we did
影響を受けなかったのかもしれません
the update but no we just don't have
更新しますが、私たちは持っていません
virgins Hyperloop one company has signed
Hyperloop one companyが署名したバージン
a deal with the government of Saudi
サウジ政府との取引
Arabia
アラビア
to build a test track for its futuristic
その未来のためのテストトラックを構築する
transport concept the Hyperloop concept
トランスポートコンセプトハイパーループコンセプト
involves a pressurized pod with a
加圧ポッドと
vehicle carrying passengers or cargo up
乗客または貨物を運ぶ車両
to ten times faster than current rail a
現在のレールよりも10倍高速
35 kilometer track will be built
35キロメートルのトラックが建設されます
alongside a research and development
研究開発と並んで
facility and manufacturing plant north
施設および製造工場北
of Jeddah some remain skeptical that
ジェッダの一部は懐疑的なまま
Hyperloop travel can become a reality
ハイパーループ旅行は現実になることができます
virgin Hyperloop one said the technology
処女ハイパーループ1は、技術を言った
could reduce a journey from rider to
ライダーからの旅を減らすことができます
Jetta to 76 minutes compared with more
より多くと比較して76分にジェッタ
than 10 hours currently Wow the company
現在10時間以上
showed off a pod traveling at over 100
100以上で移動するポッドを披露しました
kilometers an hour or a 62 miles per
時速キロメートルまたはあたり62マイル
hour in a 500 meter vacuum tube in
500メートルの真空管で1時間
Nevada in July 2017 meanwhile Elon Musk
2017年7月のネバダ州、一方イーロン・マスク
has been running an annual competition
毎年恒例の大会を開催しています
at his SpaceX headquarters to test the
SpaceXの本部で
limits of the technology this year's
今年の技術の限界
contest was won by an engineering team
コンテストはエンジニアリングチームが優勝しました
from a Technical University of Munich
ミュンヘン工科大学から
afterwards mr. musk tweeted the 2020
その後、ミスター。ムスクが2020年をツイート
event would be run in a new 10 kilometre
イベントは新しい10キロメートルで実行されます
curved vacuum tunnel Oh exciting yeah I
曲がった真空トンネル
think it's going to happen I know that
それが起こると思う私はそれを知っている
there are people who are skeptical I
懐疑的な人がいますI
feel like fast travel is it's gonna be
高速旅行のように感じます
hot right like because there are so many
たくさんあるからね
cities
都市
densely populated cities and people want
人口密度の高い都市と人々が望む
to get from one to the other there's
一方から他方へ行くには
gonna be so much time and attention put
たくさんの時間と注意を払うつもりです
into this but it will be a thing that'll
これになりますが、それは
happen in our lifetime like by 2012 as
2012年までに
we've seen in the past though I think it
過去に見たことがありますが
just comes down to with the speed if
次の場合は速度になります
something is going to go wrong it's
何かがうまくいかないだろう
going to go catastrophic ly wrong right
壊滅的に全く間違って行くつもり
and I think that's the danger or the
それが危険か
hesitation in a lot of cases because
多くの場合、ためらい
it's not a small thing it's like an
それは小さなものではなく、
airplane like it's like it's devastating
まるで壊滅的であるかのような飛行機
if an airplane goes down I don't
飛行機が落ちても私はしません
devastating if one of these things
これらのいずれかが壊滅的な場合
crashes right but there is no mode of
クラッシュしますが、モードはありません
transportation that we do that doesn't
私たちが行う輸送はそうではありません
have some level
ある程度のレベルがある
walking in the winter like you there is
あなたのように冬を歩く
no mode of transportation that can't
できない交通手段はありません
potentially hurt you
潜在的にあなたを傷つける
right so Hyperloop yes because of the
そうだからハイパーループはい
speed could kill you faster it's not a
スピードはあなたをより速く殺す可能性があります
dark spell is riskless and we all drive
ダークスペルはリスクがなく、私たち全員が運転します
those so we might as well cut down the
それらを削減するために
time to travel from one place to another
ある場所から別の場所へ旅行する時間
I know that there are risks but they'll
リスクがあることは知っていますが、
be so scared of the bad press of having
持っているという悪い報道をとても怖がる
an injury that they're gonna prevent
彼らが防ぐつもりだ怪我
that as as much as they can
彼らができる限り
yeah I think I think we're gonna be
ええ、私たちはそうなると思う
surprised Robby because there's this
これがあるのでロビーを驚かせた
huge push of like green transportation
エコ輸送のような大きなプッシュ
and that's true too you know I know I'm
そしてそれは本当ですあなたは私が知っていることを知っています
a hypocrite cuz I'm a I'm like oh I'll
偽善者だから私はそうだ
save the environment meanwhile I'm
その間、環境を保存します
flying airplanes at but at the same time
同時に飛行機を飛ばす
it's just like yeah it's dangerous but
ええ、危ないけど
they might start off with like cargo
彼らは貨物のように始まるかもしれません
first and just say hey yeah
最初にちょっと言って
let's use it for mail or just-in-time
メールやジャストインタイムに使用しましょう
shipping and then they can expand to
出荷し、彼らはに展開することができます
passengers from there but yeah it's like
そこから乗客が、ええ、それはのようなものです
a green way to send people from Montreal
モントリオールから人々を送るグリーンな方法
to Toronto or New York New York to in an
トロントまたはニューヨークへニューヨークへ
unbelievably short amount of time really
信じられないほど短い時間
good point with the cargo okay so there
貨物の良い点だからそこに
are places what are they called like are
彼らが好きな場所は
they called urban deserts where there's
彼らはそこにある都市の砂漠と呼ばれます
no food in that particular like no fresh
特に新鮮なもののような食べ物はありません
food in that part of the city
街のその部分の食べ物
imagine if they were just if they had
彼らが持っていた場合だけであった場合を想像してください
hyper loops that could just like truck
トラックのようなハイパーループ
and Masum out so and then by truck I
そしてマスムが出てトラックで
mean Hyperloop pod a potted hot in like
ハイパーループポッドを意味します。
fresh produce and and it would happen so
新鮮な食材とそれがそうなるだろう
quickly and efficiently that wouldn't
迅速かつ効率的に
cost anything to feed these urban
これらの都市を養うために費用がかかります
centers that really rely on nothing but
本当に何にも依存していないセンター
frozen food because space is an issue as
冷凍食品はスペースが問題であるため
well right but the thing is that there
よく正しいが、問題はそこにあるということです
it's expensive because like they're
彼らがそうであるように、それは高価です
digging the tunnels underground but it
地下トンネルを掘るが
also saves space above ground right so
地上のスペースも節約できます
you don't have to build another highway
別の高速道路を建設する必要はありません
you can actually put stuff you need
実際に必要なものを置くことができます
there instead of a roadway hmm so that
道路の代わりにうーんので、
can also save space too I like that what
スペースも節約できます
do you guys think I'm eager to see what
あなたは私が何を見たいと思っていると思いますか
what comes of it yeah yet another
それから何がうん
crowdfunded game has become an exclusive
クラウドファンディングゲームが独占的になりました
to epic game store MechWarrior 5
壮大なゲームストアMechWarrior 5へ
mercenaries release has been delayed to
merc兵のリリースが遅れました
december and it won't be on Steam as
12月、それはSteamにはありません
backers had expected it's becoming a
支援者は、それが
familiar story as what was a crowdfunded
クラウドファンディングであったものとしておなじみの物語
game expected to be available everywhere
ゲームはどこでも利用可能になると予想される
has become an epic game store exclusive
壮大なゲームストア独占になりました
for the next 12 months that means it
次の12か月間は
won't be available on Steam despite many
多くの場合でもSteamで利用できません
who have already pre-ordered it doing so
すでにそれを予約している人
with the assumption that it would be
であるという仮定で
it's hardly the first time that that's
それが初めてではない
happened though as epic continues to
叙事詩が続くようにしかし起こった
sign up as many games as possible to
できるだけ多くのゲームにサインアップする
keep them off steam as frustrating as it
それと同じくらいイライラさせないでください
is the anger with which PC gamers have
PCゲーマーが持っている怒りです
treated the trend has been extreme even
傾向が極端であることを扱った
by gamer standards but epic shows no
ゲーマーの基準によるが、叙事詩はいいえを示しています
sign of backing down and maintains it's
バックダウンのサインとそれを維持します
the best way to establish their online
オンラインを確立する最良の方法
store on their blog developer piranha
ブログ開発者ピラニアに保存
games has said that they'll refund
ゲームは払い戻しをすると言っています
anyone that isn't happy about the news
ニュースに満足していない人
as long as they get in contact by
彼らが接触する限り
September 1st the other big news story
9月1日、もう一つのビッグニュース
for the game though is that it's been
ゲームのためにしかしそれはされているということです
delayed from its original release date
元のリリース日から遅延
of September 10th to December 10th of
9月10日から12月10日まで
this year that said a closed beta is now
今年はクローズドベータが
planned for November and anyone anyone
11月と誰でも計画されています
that's pre-ordered it will get automatic
事前注文されているため、自動で取得されます
access to several of the final games
いくつかの最終ゲームへのアクセス
practice missions
練習ミッション
that's interesting almost feels like
おもしろいです
they're giving it more time like okay
彼らは大丈夫のようにより多くの時間を与えている
epic has bought it and now they're gonna
叙事詩はそれを買って、今彼らはつもりだ
put it through its paces before it's
それの前にそのペースを試してください
released to make sure that it's up to
リリースされていることを確認する
epic standards can you say how many
叙事詩の基準
people do you think are gonna be so
人々はそうなると思いますか
upset about this news they'll ask for a
彼らが求めるこのニュースについての動揺
refund right unless you want to opt into
あなたがオプトインしたくない限り、権利を払い戻します
your early access but your early access
あなたの早期アクセスがあなたの早期アクセス
is still later than the original release
元のリリースよりもまだ遅い
date yeah what did this take away from
ええ、これは何を奪ったのですか
the funding of a like of developing it
開発のようなものの資金
beyond from September through December
9月から12月まで
when they see how many people want a
何人が欲しいかを見ると
refund yeah if it was a mask you funding
払い戻しは、それがあなたが資金を提供するマスクだった場合
is so tell there won't be a mask gamer
マスクゲーマーはいないと伝えてください
movement there will be but the big thing
動きがありますが、大きなこと
with epic right now is that they have
壮大な今は彼らが持っているということです
the money to support it and the main
それを支えるお金とメイン
issue with epic versus steam is that
エピック対スチームの問題は
epic is letting the game developers get
エピックはゲーム開発者に
more money out of it right so let's say
より多くのお金が正しいので、言いましょう
if steam charges 10% commission but when
蒸気が10％の手数料を請求する場合、ただし
they sell a game epic would only slight
彼らはゲームの叙事詩を売ります
charge 5% right so there's an
5％の権利を請求するので、
inclination of yeah we should go to epic
ええ、私たちは叙事詩に行くべきです
but again epic doesn't have all the same
しかし、再び叙事詩はすべて同じではありません
good features everything else that steam
優れた機能は、他のすべての蒸気
does so a lot of gamers are angry
そう多くのゲーマーが怒っています
because epic is stealing cool unquote
叙事詩は引用符なしでクールを盗んでいるので
stealing again both says argument their
再び盗むことは両方の引数を言います
games because there's a lot of
ゲームがたくさんあるので
Kickstarter games there's a lot of these
Kickstarterゲームにはこれらがたくさんあります
games like I think Phoenix Point Shenmue
フェニックスポイントシェンムーと思うゲーム
all these other games that we're gonna
私たちがしようとしている他のすべてのゲーム
be on Steam we're marketed as being on
Steam上にあります
Steam but now epic has paid them out pay
蒸気が、今叙事詩はそれらを支払った
them out and now they're only gonna be
それらを外し、今彼らはするつもりです
epic exclusive or epic exclusive for X
X専用のエピックエクスクルーシブまたはエピックエクスクルーシブ
amount of time right so it's really
正しい時間なので、本当に
sucky for the players right um if it
プレイヤーにとってはうんざりだ
matters if you like steam or not but it
あなたが蒸気が好きかどうかは重要ですが、それは
just both steam and epic you can but
スチームとエピックの両方が可能ですが、
there's a as there's been a lot of
たくさんあったように
controversy about epic fell like there's
叙事詩についての論争があったように落ちました
been a lot of in the sense that a it
それという意味でたくさんありました
doesn't have a lot of basic features so
基本的な機能があまりないので
like when you log into steam obviously
あなたが明らかに蒸気にログインするときのように
have a games but there's like a lot of
ゲームがありますが、たくさんあります
social market community things but with
ソーシャルマーケットコミュニティのもの
epic game launcher there's been some
壮大なゲームランチャーがいくつかありました
like security issue
セキュリティ問題のような
Jews again don't quote me on this you
ユダヤ人は再びこのあなたに私を引用しない
can google it yourself but um there's
自分でグーグルで検索できますが、
been like a lot of controversy about
について多くの論争のようでした
that right because with epic store they
エピックストアでは彼らが
don't have a lot of infrastructure with
インフラストラクチャがあまりない
that that being said it's still a new
それはまだ新しいと言われていること
idea right it's still a new store which
アイデアはまだ新しい店です
is great for the consumer you think
あなたが思う消費者に最適です
because more competition better pricing
より多くの競争がより良い価格設定のため
right but the issue is that steam isn't
正しいが、問題は蒸気が
doing another thing to counteract this
これに対抗するために別のことをする
right if steam wants to win all they
スチームがすべてを勝ち取りたいなら
have to do is lure the Commission cost
しなければならないのは、委員会のコストを誘惑することです
of selling a game to like 5% oh right
ゲームを売って、5％が好き
and the owners of epic has have actually
そして叙事詩の所有者は実際に持っています
said look if you lower your costs we'll
コストを下げると見て
stop stealing games if you believe them
あなたがそれらを信じる場合、ゲームを盗むのをやめる
or not that's your choice right but it's
それはあなたの選択の権利ですが、それは
it's literally come down to that so it's
それは文字通りそれまで来ているので
just it's mixed feelings right now
ちょうど今は複雑な気持ちです
throughout the community I'm fairly new
コミュニティ全体で私はかなり新しいです
to steam I only ended up getting steam
蒸気を発するようになった
when I got my VR butthead tech yeah so
VR butthead techを手に入れたとき
that's when I was introduced to steam
それは私が蒸気に導入されたときです
but I don't know about epoch at all I
しかし、私はエポックについて全く知りません
don't know I don't know a lot about the
よくわからない
politics between the two I didn't I just
ふたりの間の政治
expected well if you want to play a game
あなたがゲームをプレイしたい場合はよく期待
it's fine just play a game right and
ゲームを正しくプレイすれば大丈夫です
like nothing says you can't enjoy epic
何も言わずにあなたは叙事詩を楽しむことができないと言う
like it has plenty of positives but
たくさんの良い点があるけど
again as I move abayas Linux steam etc I
再びabayas Linux steamなどを移動すると
first see myself but again if that
最初に自分自身を見ます
doesn't matter to you if you still want
あなたがまだ欲しいならあなたには関係ありません
to play your awesome game on a different
別のであなたの素晴らしいゲームをプレイする
platform power to you do that right but
あなたへのプラットフォームの力はそれを正しくしますが、
whose epic friend Wes like uh epic is
その叙事詩の友人Wesはええ叙事詩が好きです
run by epic and why because like there's
叙事詩によって実行され、なぜあるので
a what is it there's unity and then
それは一体であり、それから何ですか
there's uh what's the other game Unreal
他のゲームUnrealは何ですか
Engine yeah epic owns Unreal Engine oh
Engine yeah epicはUnreal Engineを所有しています
so like it's the same company so it's
同じ会社のように
like the same launcher so it's just like
同じランチャーのようにそれはちょうどのようです
I dabbled in like Unreal Engine for a
アンリアルエンジンのように手を出しました
bit it's like the same launcher so it's
ビットは同じランチャーのようなものなので、
just like you have your game creation
ゲームを作成するように
engine and then you have like your epic
エンジン、そしてあなたはあなたの叙事詩が好きです
game store and then you have all these
ゲームストア、そしてあなたはこれらすべてを持っています
other things but it's just that they're
他のことですが、それは彼らがいるということだけです
swimming in the fort night money right
砦の夜のお金で泳ぐ権利
now
今
not sure yes yeah and part of that is we
確かではないです。その一部は私たちです
don't want to give away our Commission
委員会を譲りたくない
that's the thing right yes so steam
はい、そうです
steam isn't doing anything but they
スチームは何もしていませんが、彼らは
don't really have to do anything right
本当に何もする必要はありません
now because there's a lot of there they
今はたくさんあるから
still have a large user base that say we
まだ私たちを言う大規模なユーザーベースを持っています
like our market we like our everything
市場のように、私たちはすべてのものが好きです
right so brand loyal brand loyalty
そうブランド忠実なブランドの忠誠心
comment below if it affects you or how
以下にコメントする
you feel about it personally I'm I'm in
あなたは個人的にそれについて感じます私は私がいる
different stores a store
異なる店舗
yeah install either or or both or well
ええ、どちらか、または両方、またはうまくインストールします
yeah they say it the thing I would say
ええ、彼らは私が言うことを言う
about it is I am on Steam and I wouldn't
それについては私はSteamにいると私はしないだろう
I wouldn't have thought to go elsewhere
他に行こうとは思わなかった
at all I didn't know yeah but if another
まったく知りませんでしたが、別の場合
game says you need epic then game stores
ゲームは壮大なゲームストアが必要だと言います
right all right hey we do it anyways
よし、とにかくやる
right you have origins steam good ol
あなたは起源を持っています
games twitch well you just have more
ゲームはよく動けます
software on your computer that's all
コンピューター上のソフトウェアがすべて
there you go yeah speaking of games you
そちらでゲームの話をします
can run Android on Nintendo switch and
ニンテンドースイッチでAndroidを実行できます
it runs entirely from your SD card
SDカードから完全に実行されます
that's right the built-in OS remains
そうです、組み込みOSはそのままです
intact and you can jump back and forth
無傷で前後にジャンプできます
between OSS by simply rebooting the
単純に再起動することにより、OSS
Nintendo switch isn't a device that we
任天堂のスイッチは私たちが使用するデバイスではありません
would usually associate with Android
通常はAndroidに関連付けられます
development however thanks to the hard
しかし、ハードのおかげで開発
work by XD a senior member Langer Haynes
XDのシニアメンバー、ランガーヘインズ
and XD a junior member bylaws any
XDジュニアメンバー細則
hackable Nintendo switched typically
ハッキング可能な任天堂は通常切り替え
devices sold before July 2018 can now
2018年7月以前に販売されていたデバイスは、
we'll boot a lineage OS 15.1 directly
系統OS 15.1を直接起動します
from the SD card lineage OS 15.1 on the
SDカード系統OS 15.1から
nintendo switch has basically everything
ニンテンドースイッチは基本的にすべてを持っています
you've come to expect from lineage OS
あなたは系統OSに期待するようになりました
you get all of your basic Android
基本的なAndroidをすべて入手できます
features support for Google services and
Googleサービスのサポートと
even support for native Nvidia shield
ネイティブのNvidiaシールドもサポート
applications that means you can play
あなたがプレイできることを意味するアプリケーション
half-life and portal on-the-go and even
半減期とポータルは外出先でも
make use of GeForce now if you're part
あなたが参加しているなら、今すぐGeForceを利用してください
of the beta the joy cons and Nintendo
ベータ版の喜び短所と任天堂
pro controller work without a hitch
支障なくプロのコントローラーが動作
keyboard and mouse works when docked
キーボードとマウスはドッキング時に機能します
pretty much anything that can work will
動作するものはほとんど何でも
work it's a spectacular port of Android
動作しますAndroidの壮大なポートです
and one that's well worth setting up if
そしてもし設定する価値があるもの
you have a spare SD card installing
予備のSDカードを取り付けています
Android on your Nintendo switch does not
ニンテンドースイッチのAndroidは
touch the main OS installed on it so you
インストールされているメインOSをタッチして、
don't need to worry about breaking
壊れることを心配する必要はありません
anything if you want to get started
始めたいなら何でも
check out the switch root lineage OS
スイッチのルート系統のOSを確認してください
15.1 thread we've hotlinked at cat5
15.1 cat5でホットリンクしたスレッド
dot TV slash switch switch android
ドットテレビスラッシュスイッチスイッチアンドロイド
switch Android I cut off a little bit on
Androidを切り替えます
the teleprompter but I knew it because I
テレプロンプターが、私はそれを知っていた
wrote it that is too cool absolutely
絶対にクールすぎると書いた
awesome I mean you feel kind of limited
すごいな
by what the switch provides but it's
スイッチが提供するものによってですが、それは
fantastic I mean the kids love it and it
幻想的だよ
does everything they need it to do but
彼らがするために必要なことはすべてしますが、
to be able to take it and turn it into a
それを取り、それを
tablet at the same time now all of a
同時にタブレットすべての
sudden a take your tablet with you take
突然あなたとタブレットを取る
your switch with you it's just all one
あなたとあなたのスイッチはそれだけです
device that's great perfect I love that
とても完璧なデバイスが大好きです
you could just do it with the SD card
あなたはSDカードでそれを行うことができます
you don't have to do anything to the
あなたは何もする必要はありません
built-in storage
内蔵ストレージ
yeah there's no risk at all anything you
ええ、あなたには何のリスクもありません
can do it oh there's always risk we'll
私たちができるリスクは常にあります
find a way to break it but yeah that's
それを破る方法を見つけるが、ええそれは
cool very good stuff big thanks to Roy W
Roy Wに感謝
Nash in our community of yours for
私たちのコミュニティのナッシュ
submitting stories to us this week
今週私たちに物語を提出する
thanks for watching the category-five TV
カテゴリー5のテレビを見てくれてありがとう
newsroom don't forget to Like and
ニュースルームは「いいね」することを忘れないでください
subscribe for all your tech news with a
ですべての技術ニュースを購読する
slight linux biased and for more free
わずかなLinuxバイアスがかかり、さらに無料
content be sure to check out our web
コンテンツは必ずウェブをご覧ください
site from the category-five TV newsroom
カテゴリ5のテレビニュースルームのサイト
I'm Sasha Rickman and I'm Robbie
私はサーシャ・リックマン、ロビーです
Ferguson and I'm Mary Bailey bro
ファーガソンと私はメアリー・ベイリー兄弟です
[Music]
[音楽]